ANTON MARAIS

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

^	082 444 0023	
<u> </u>	info@studio81.info	\bowtie
~_	www.studio81.info	
	Centurion, Pretoria	ñ

≟ ≡



ALL ABOUT ME

NAME Anton Marais

ID

8110145158084

LANGUAGE

Afikaans (Read & Write) English (Read & Write)

Martial Status

Married

ADRESS

Centurion, Pretoria

COVER LETTER

Hi, I'm Anton a passionate Graphic Designer with a wide variety of skills. In terms of my career, graphic design has always been my first choice.

Due to financial constraints I had to pursue other options and my full-time graphic design had to be put on the back burner for a while. During this time, I obtained my N3, wiremen, and Red Seal, and I started my own Electrical company.

At present I am committed to continue my career as a graphic designer. My love for designing and creating are still number one. Admiration and client satisfaction for your creation, is something I pride myself in.

And if given the opportunity I will be an asset to your team

ANTON MARAIS

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

082 444 0023	
info@studio81.info	\bowtie
www.studio81.info	~
Centurion, Pretoria	ñ

: ≡



EDUCATION

CERTIFICATE

CTU College - Graphic Design 10March-16April 2008

EXPERTISE

Graphic Design

Indesign

- Layouts
- Cover Designs
- Business Cards
- Letterheads

Illustrator/Corel

- Vector Ilustrations
- Vector Art
- Branding
- Logo's
- Email Signature

Photoshop

- Editing Photos
- Retouch Photos
- Photo Manipulation
- Color Correction

ABOUT ME

I worked for a Car magazine designing covers, features, layouts, and adverts for different products. I also worked for a medical company designing all their products packaging, labels, printable banners, and adverts.

I Specialize in graphic design with Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Corel Draw, and Indesign. For the car magazine, I retouched most of the car photos in photoshop and handled the layout in InDesign.

Corel and illustrator is my go-to program for packaging design and I also use them to make stickers and car wraps.

WORK EXPERIENCE

November 2011 - September 2012

O GRAPHIC DESIGNER -

IEComm's

lecomms was a design house that specialized in all things graphic & marketing related.

I designed a vast array of projects here. designs included adverts for the State Theatre. The logo design was also done here and I used Illustrator or Corel for these elements. Banners had to be done with InDesign and editing of photos for the banners would go with photoshop.

January 2009 - January 2011

• GRAPHIC DESIGNER -

Zinplex

Zinplex was a medical company that specialized in supplements & vitamins. My task there was to design product packaging and labels for their products. When they had expos i had to design all the relevant material such as pull up banners, flags, and content for the booths. I also had to design adverts for the newspapers and magazine's.

January 2008 - February 2009

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Max My Ride Magazine

A printable car magazine where I had to do most of the designing.

I designed mostly the covers for the magazine. For the cover of the magazine, I had to manipulate, retouch or edit photos to work with font selections and main highlights of the magazine itself. For the inside of the magazine, I had to design the layout and all the other graphical elements like the adverts and features with mostly photoshop and InDesign. For all other vector elements, I had to use illustrator